Collin Page

(615)-426-1187 - collin.page0809@gmail.com - https://github.com/colpage

Computer Information Systems graduate with a lifelong interest in computer technology. IT specialist with 4+ years of experience working in professional environments with stringent security requirements. Constantly striving to improve knowledge of technology and administrative requirements to be met by businesses.

CORE SKILLS

LAN ConfigurationKali LinuxTCP/IP FundamentalsEndpoint SecurityWindows / MAC OSI.T. TroubleshootingGithubCommand Prompt / PowerShellHIPAA Regulations

Languages: SQL, Python, C#, HTML & CSS

Applications: Active Directory, Banner 8, Sophos, Visual Studio, Tableau, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Jira/Confluence

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School

Data Analytics Boot Camp

Nashville, TN

Expected Graduation July 2021

Middle Tennessee State University

Bachelors Computer Information Systems Major

• Business Minor

Murfreesboro, TN Graduated Dec 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trinisys Healthcare Data Engineering

Infrastructure Support

Troubleshot software and hardware for 70 users across multiple departments

Brentwood, TN

Assisted in tech support for systems secured by HIPAA and HITRUST policies

Dec 2019 - Present

Participated in full office move transferring local servers, switches, and access points

Middle Tennessee State University

ITD Help Desk

Murfreesboro, TN Dec 2017 – Dec 2019

- Provided IT support for 20,000 students and professors on campus
- Understood LAN/WAN and internet/intranet and its impact on the device environment of MTSU
- Trained 15 personnel on effective troubleshooting practices involving basic networking concepts, Active Directory,
 Footprints, cookie tracking, and PII management

MILITARY EXPERIENCE

Aviation Mechanic

United States Navy - Honorable Discharge

Jacksonville, FL

Maintained and repaired CFM-52B engines attached to the P-8 Orion aircraft

Jan 2013 - May 2016

- Assisted VP-30 in training 800 officer and enlisted personnel annually
- Participated in launch and catch operations, aircraft towing, and routine maintenance procedures